So Anthropic has released their most
powerful model just yesterday, and they're
calling it Fable. And it's the first Methos
class uh model. If you don't know what
Mythos is, Mythos is the model that
they announced about a month ago,
and they said that they're gonna release it in
public because it's uh extremely powerful,
and it found security holes in the software
that has been used for many, many years.
Uh and it's it's critical, like everybody
is using it like Linux kernel and open SSL.
So finding the security holes in that and
not only the security holes, but also found
the exploits as well, is extremely critical.
So what they did was before actually
you know releasing it to the public,
they said that they are gonna have a control
release, and they actually gave it to like big
companies uh so that they can
plug their security holes.
However, yesterday Anthropic
went ahead and released that
model, but with some guardrails.
So they took Mythos put guardrails around it,
and they released it, and they're
calling it Fable, Fable 5.
So this model is supposedly an extremely
powerful model that is available to
the public, and people are
extremely excited about it.
So today we are gonna put it to test.
We are gonna build an app
with it and see how it does.
I haven't used Fable yet, and this is
the first time I'm gonna be using it, and
I'll take you guys along and see how it
performs while building the app.
I built a lot of apps with Sonnet, Opus,
and uh Gemini and recently with
GPT 5.5 and they all do really good. But you
have to go back and forth quite a bit with them.
Uh but this model fable is supposed to
basically surpass all these models.
So I'm assuming that it's gonna
do way better than the other models, and
we won't have to go back and forth too much.
So we will create an app
that will allow the users
to actually look for jobs and apply for them.
Um so the app is gonna go out there,
seek out the available jobs.
Uh based on their criteria or the
keywords that they have placed.
It is gonna
list those jobs to the user, and then the
user can actually and apply for those jobs.
So let's see if it is able
to handle something like
this. Okay, so this is the Claude Code user
interface. It's a desktop application.
If you haven't used Cloud Code before, you can
just uh search on Claude Desktop and download
it based on your operating system from here.
So just download and install it on your
computer, and then you will get an interface
like this. If you're new to Claude Desktop,
there are three tabs here. You can use uh chat
to just uh chat with the Claude and you can use
uh co work that will allow you to actually um.
Interact with your desktop.
You can do a lot of things with the Claude
which are gonna be local to your computer
itself, like that's gonna deal with
your files and folders on your hard drive. So
you can use those, but be very careful with it.
Don't let it actually delete
your stuff that is very critical.
And then there is uh code
tab, and you can actually
go ahead and have Cloud write code for you.
So you can build your applications here.
So we are gonna use uh Claude code to do that.
Now they have a terminal also which
is more advanced and uh tricky to use.
So I'm gonna use just this user interface so
that anybody can actually use it, you know.
Anybody who is not very well versed with uh
using terminals, they can use it as well.
So let's try it out. So here's the thing.
First thing that you want to do is
to actually select local here.
You want to build the application locally
first before you can upload it anywhere.
So we are gonna be building the application
locally, so that all the files are actually
residing on your local hard
drive. That's how I build.
Uh there is um there is that cloud
option also, but we are not gonna
go with that today. Once you have local, it
will allow you to actually select the folder.
You can basically click on it
and it will open up your file
explorer, and you could basically go ahead
and create the folder where you want the
entire application to reside. That's very
important. You should do that. You should
create a separate folder so
that all the files related to
the project are in one particular folder.
So I already created this job search apply
folder, and that's what I have selected.
Now the other thing that you want to do is click
on here, and it will give you option for all
the models that are available. So you
could use the Opus models if you want to.
And uh if you want to use, you can
use Sonnet So the hierarchy is
Haiku is the lowest and cheapest.
And then Sonnet is pretty good.
Not so expensive, not so cheap.
It's in the middle mid range,
and it's very smart also.
So it has been the king for long time,
like just three, four months ago.
Now there are better models than this,
like Opus, which comes on top of it.
It's more expensive, way more expensive,
and way more powerful than Sonic.
And that's what we have been using for more
tricky and complex work, but for any general
purpose work, Sonnet is the best option.
And then the next level now above
all Opus is supposedly fable.
Fable is even more expensive than uh Opus.
One thing to note is that Fable is available
with paid subscription until June 22nd.
So you have to have a paid
subscription. It's not available on the
free subscription. And on top of it, it is only
gonna be available until June 22nd.
So build whatever you have
to build before June 22nd.
After that, they are
gonna make it pay as you go.
So you will have to pay for every API call.
So not only you have to be
a paid member, and then on
top of it, if you want to use Fable, we'll have
to pay for it. And this thing is expensive.
Like super expensive. It will be impractical
to pay for it unless you're building something
that's gonna give you that kind of return.
But for now, Fable is available in the paid
subscription. For free. Kind of. You're
already paying for it for the subscription.
But it is mostly free to use.
And I'm sure the quota is very limited on it.
So we will see if we run out of coda
while we are building this app.
So once we have all the set, the
next thing to do is to give a prompt.
So normally when I am building
an app, I actually give it a
rough prompt, just dictate to it whatever
I want, uh, whatever comes to my mind,
and then I ask it to write a PRD for it.
And PRD is a product requirement document.
This is how we work in the corporate
environment in software engineering.
We actually write a PRD for it. Actually,
normally program manager does that.
But we have to have a PRD, which actually
roughly describes all the features of
the of the product that we want
the product to have. Right.
And then what happens is that you write the
requirement document from it, and then you
write the design document for
it, and then you implement it.
Of course, I don't go through all
this ever since I'm doing AI coding,
but I definitely write a PRD document,
which is very detailed, and I use that PRD
document to write milestone.
And then once you have different
milestones, I want to do this first,
and then this next, and then this next.
So if you divide your
app into these chunks, it's easier.
And then you give one milestone at a time to the
AI coding software and have them build the app
one milestone at a time. And that's my regular
process, and that's what you should follow.
Because if you throw everything on
it, usually the models cannot handle.
But since Fable is supposedly
a very powerful model,
we are gonna just give it a vague prompt.
And skip all this.
No PRD, no milestones, no nothing.
We are gonna ask it to write a
complete full app and see how it does.
Right.
Okay, so I have dictated the prompt here.
So I'm gonna read it out so
that you know what it is.
It says, okay, let's create a web app that
helps people search for
jobs and apply to them.
I want to use some kind of API from
Apify or another similar source.
Obviously, it's gonna use some
kind of API to find out the jobs.
So I am asking it to use
the Apify which is a very good place to use API.
If you don't know API, API is uh
is an interface to a service,
so you can talk to it, you can grab data from
it, and you can you know write data to it.
So Apify is a very good place where
they have all different kinds
of APIs available for all
different kinds of services.
So if you need anything, if you want
to access if you want your app to do
something, for example, uh if
you want to create an app which
will give you the listings of all the houses
available for rent or for to buy, you can go to
apify and you will find some.
One has developed this API for it so
that you can use it in your program.
So API actually, it's application
program and interface.
It allows you to build applications or
your own software to use other services to
be part of your application.
So I'm asking it to use
AP5, find some service there for this
purpose, because in this case we have to
find out all the jobs which are available.
And I'm sure there are some API on Apify
which actually would allow us to
retrieve all the available jobs.
You need to keep the cost as low as possible
for searching and applying to jobs.
I don't want to spend too much money,
and plus your app should not spend too
much money anyways, right?
more your cost is more is gonna
be the cost for your customer.
And more difficult it will be to actually
market that app. Create
everything from beginning to end.
I want a landing page, authentication,
backend database, payment processing.
Also describe some subscription plans and
make sure there is flexibility to change
those plans later. Now
these are very basic things.
In our app for job seeking and applying,
we will have to have authentication,
which means the user could should be able
to log in and stuff. We should be able to
store user data, anything related to user,
which jobs they have applied and which
jobs they want to apply. We want to be
able to store them to store that data.
You need some kind of database in there. And
then if you want to charge your customers,
you need some kind of payment processing
service in there as well. I have asked it to add
all these things so that it
knows the scope of the app.
There should be an admin
role and regular user roles.
The admin should be able to make
changes, create and manage
plans and handle other settings.
Regular users should be able to log
into their dashboard and see how many
new jobs are available.
How many jobs they can still apply to, and
how many jobs they have already applied for.
Make sure to cover all the corner
cases, keep the cost as low as possible, use
local services and internal functionality
as much as possible, and also use external
services when there is no better option.
Just choose the best low
cost option available.
Again, we are reminding to use the low cost.
Create .env.example file.
For any API keys or service credentials
needed for the external services.
I will fill in the real values later
for now, populate it with dummy data.
Let's clarify what it here is.
Populate the app with the dummy data,
not just the dot env example.
Now if you don't know what
.env.example file is.
Usually when you are actually using
other services, you will need some kind
of API key, which is a secret. You don't
want anybody else to know about it.
And we keep them in a
separate file called.env.
And we specify those in there, we get it
from the service and we put it in there.
And that file stays locally secured, never
gets uploaded anywhere on the internet.
Because if you upload it there, if somebody
else gets hold of it, they can use those
API keys and perform those
operations, and you pay for it.
So they'll be using the
services and you will be
paying for it. So you don't want that to
happen. So you want to keep those secured.
So we want to put them in .env file Use
Frost Glass, liquid glass theme. I like those
a lot. And I have noticed that the models have
a very hard time in building those.
So we will see how good Fable does.
Allow to change between
light theme and dark theme.
So that's all I'm giving it as the prompt.
I'm not creating any PRD. I'm not
creating any milestones or anything.
I'm gonna just throw this prompt
at it and see how well it does.
So let's go.
Before we do that, let's make sure that
we have selected Fable 5 as the model.
And it seems if you look at this uh
graph, which actually actually compares
the top three models, Fable 5,
Opus 4.8, and GPT 5.5.
Right.
So if you look at the on this scale,
there is uh cost and uh on this scale, it's the
performance score, whatever the score that
they're using.
But this gives us a rough idea
of how these models compare.
So we have this uh GPT 5.5, which is really
good model, actually, somewhere here.
Of course, it doesn't belong to Anthropic
so they're gonna just uh do that.
But it is very close to
Opus, actually, by the way.
But I mean probably not as good as the Opus is,
but it's not as far as they've
shown here, in my opinion.
So anyway, this is the line for GPT 5.5,
and there are always different levels.
So low, medium, high, and extra high.
As you go higher
in the level, usually the cost increases,
but according to them, the performance is
not increasing as much. So which is very
weird. I don't think that's the case.
But anyway, for opus, as you can see,
even for opus, they're saying the
medium is performing less than low.
So opus is falling here,
but you can see that Fable is way up here.
So if you'll use Fable in extra high and max,
this is gonna just blow your mind, I would
think, if this these numbers are correct. But
what they are telling us that low, fable low is
better than GPD high and extra high,
and it costs almost the same as these models.
So and it's even better than high, opus high.
So we are gonna select low, which is
supposedly better than all these
models, and see how it does.
Because if I select medium, high, or extra
high, I'm sure it's gonna run out of my quota
you know, before it has
even completed the app.
So I'm gonna select it to
low and see how that goes.
So here we are gonna select low for it.
So we are gonna keep it at fable five low,
and then we are gonna submit it to Fable and
see. How it does. Now there are a lot of things
that you could specify, like what kind
of framework you're gonna be using, like
React and stuff. I haven't done that.
I haven't specified what kind of
database I'm gonna be using and all this.
Normally, as I said, when
we create PRD and stuff,
you do specify all this. We haven't done that.
I hope that it's gonna make a good selection.
I hope it's gonna select React
for this particular app.
And some database other than
Superbase or something like
maybe the local database, maybe sqlite just
to for the PRD. But we'll see how that goes.
Okay, so it's asking me to use um
PowerShell and uh asking for permission.
So I'm gonna say always allow.
So that it doesn't ask me again for that.
So it's saying I'll build complete job search
and apply web app using nextGS and SQLite.
Okay, so it decided to use
nextGS. That's fine. NextGS is good also. I
would have preferred React, but that's fine.
We can we can work with the next GS.
And it decided to use Skill
Light, so which is good.
This way we can just have a free local
test. To see how things are working, and then
if you want to go further, we can always ask it
to actually switch it to some other database.
Key based JWT Auth. So this is also good.
It's like local authentication protocol
comes with Next.js. Maybe that's the reason
why it's using Next.js. And so we don't have to
use any external services uh for that.
And then it's gonna use the Stripe for
payments, which is also a good payment
processing service. I wanted to
use it. Actually, I didn't say it.
Uh I usually use the Stripe with a built-in
mock mode, so it runs without keys.
So it will also create a mock mode,
which is mock data is basically data which
is not true data, but just to test the app,
it will basically populate the app with those
that data so that we can do perform actions on
it. Because otherwise, without data, how
would you actually tell? How would you log in?
You know, you will have to create real users
and you'll have to search for the real jobs and
stuff like that. But just to test how the
things need to work, we always create mock
data, and that actually
allows us to test the app.
And then it's saying that it's gonna use the
frost glass UI and all this, so that's that'll
be good. And it's doing all these
one by the one at a time, one by one.
It's right now working on auth API and route.
Now it's working on APIs to actually
retrieve jobs with code and force.
Looks like uh it's basically
going to apply some coda to the
users also, which is a good thing.
Because we don't want the users to
actually sign up, just keep
on getting the job listings.
They are not gonna have infinite access to the
to getting the job, because obviously every
query that they are gonna do, it's gonna cost
us money because those API
calls are gonna cost us money.
So we will have to have some kind of uh
code and it never told it about this,
and it automatically looks like it's
gonna it has decided to do that, which is a
very, very good thing. Now these APIs could be
actually local APIs that it's talking about.
These are the APIs to talk to our application.
Not the API to actually go out and
uh retrieve the data about jobs.
And it is showing here how much uh tokens
it has or the code arm it has already used.
So it breaks it into five
hour limit and weekly limit.
Codex also does the
same thing. It's saying that it has already
used 11. I had used it a little bit more before.
This 11% is actually from the
beginning of this app development, but I had
used uh the weekly coda, this 10% actually
has some other stuff, not just this app, but
it's going pretty fast as well, it seems uh
uh which is not good, but uh we'll see how that
goes. I hope it doesn't run out of coda before
the app is completed. So it's asking to
actually see the database. Uh we are gonna say
yes, which actually means that it's gonna
be populated with some uh data, mock data
that it's gonna generate. I'm going to let
it continue and uh come back when it's done.
Let's take a look what it has done.
Okay, so it looks like it created the.
So that we can look at the
information about the about the app.
It has also done a lot of testing.
So it says that login works uh so
it looks like it tested the login.
It has some issue with the locking the
database being locked because of the
server running would
stop it and then re-ran it.
And then it says everything passes, so it ran
all the tests also, so which is a really good
thing because testing is essential part of
soft change engineering cycle for for an app
development. Right. So um and then
it gave us uh the whole uh summary.
So let's see.
It's calling it job glass,
kind of a weird name.
But that's fine.
Uh a complete next year next JS
um app router plus transcript uh app.
Designed around minimum cost, everything
runs locally with zero external
keys required. That's uh kind of surprising.
I would expect that it would need some keys.
Oh, I think it's talking about that with mock
data, you could be run it without any keys, so
which is good. And the stack that
it chose, database that's using uh
scale light, which is fine, auth.
It said that you know it's
gonna use GWT with B crypt to
uh uh secure passwords, which is uh
which is a good good acceptable solution.
It's uh using a stripe for that with no keys,
it's just gonna use the mock mode where you
know you could uh check out without going
through actual stripe, which is a good thing.
That way we can test, we can create users
and we can basically just uh upgrade
their plans without paying a
single penny in the test mode.
And then the most important
thing, uh job data.
Uh it's using Apify integration that only
reads the last successful
actor run's data data set.
Which is uh which has some kind of
mechanism that goes and does uh actor
run, grabs the data and uh then reuses it.
It doesn't go every time run the APIs,
so that to keep the cost minimum.
So it is really working on the fact
that it doesn't want to use uh a lot of uh money
to actually uh uh scrap the for jobs.
And then it has glass themed
landing page, pricing,
login register, user dashboard, and all
those uh cool things that we need to have.
We are gonna look at the app in a moment.
Let's see, and it also has uh
it has uh defined a free plan
with zero it allows five applies per month.
So you can apply for five jobs every month,
and the pro has uh nine dollars per month,
and you can have unlimited jobs.
We are minus one, which means if you put minus
one in the database, it says that you know
you can unlimited jobs.
So all this is good, and it also lists
all these corner cases which uh which
uh include really real cool things like um
auto-downgrade to free, which is which is
a corner case, which is the pretty difficult
to actually handle if you have ever built app
before and monthly codas roll forward.
Okay, I never asked it to do that.
I don't think I want to do I would like
the coda to roll forward because
it accumulates uh too much and costs
you money, but we know that that's good
missing subscription auto-attach
free, which is uh which is shy web
signature verification with recharge,
I'm just reading random, so you're this is
this is a very good thing too it has the logins,
it has a seed seed logins uh admin is at uh
this uh uh email address and this password.
And there are gonna be two roles,
one is admin and one is uh user.
So it has created one user for
uh uh admin role and one user for the user
role, so that we can look at both sides,
uh administration side of the website as
well as the user side of the website.
This is also very important.
It's almost always in every application you
will have this that you will have to create
a admin user as well as uh the regular users.
And then it's asking us to fill in
the uh API keys in dot env.example.
It uses the stripe and
Apify keys looks like, and that has also
created readme with all the steps, and you can
run the server with npm and dev,
which is a normal thing to do.
Okay, so this is very interesting. It
says that the currently the demo user,
because of the testing
is on the unlimited plan.
If you want to change it, it says that we run npm
run dev:seed It will it is gonna
reseed the database.
And then it in the bracket itself,
it's saying it's actually
denying what it's just said, and
it's actually correcting itself.
It says uh it won't it won't do that, actually.
It's not gonna reseed your database because
if the data is already existing, it doesn't
actually reseed.
So just go in into the admin
admin panel and uh change it from there, which
which is the right thing to do, actually.
I should be able to go and do that.
It's it's funny. It said something, and then
after that in brackets, it's saying that no,
this is not gonna work, it should be done
this way. I find it very funny for such a smart
uh model.
But after all,
these are models. Okay, so moment of truth.
How are we going to access this app, right?
But then it has given us this URL.
And if you click on it, it opens it up.
So look at that.
Job glass.
Your job search beautifully organized.
I can see it off the bat that this is
actually out a little bit on the
fonts here, but that's fine.
That can easily be fixed.
Get started, it's free, view pricing,
fresh listings, one click apply
tracking, know your numbers.
Okay.
And then simple pricing.
Free get started.
Browse jobs. And apply to f few each
month. Five applications per month.
Pro nine dollars per month for active seeker.
And unlimited. Okay. Landing
page is pretty short. That's fine.
And then we have toggle this is the dark theme.
And we're gonna go back to light team.
And then this is uh supposed
to have some contract.
S sign up is actually
hiding behind this uh background.
So it's overall good, but
not unusually uh awesome.
Then hey, let's see.
Uh we'll we'll we'll see
how the functionality is.
If I click on pricing, it
opens up a pricing page,
which is separate from that page, and it lists
uh more detailed pricing
information, which is good.
Now let's uh take a look
at the let's try to log in.
The login page looks pretty good.
Um let's see.
Let's log in as uh admin first.
So it says that this is what the username
is, and then admin one to three, and
then this is what the password is.
We're gonna log in, or we have uh dashboard,
and we have more options here, which is good.
So it has the admin dashboard,
it shows how many users do we have total,
and how many active jobs we have and
uh applications, how many people
overall, I guess, have applied to
jobs, so there are five applications
and there is one paying subscriber.
So it gives the overall view of what
going on with the entire app.
Um so here are the plans, different plans.
Free plan has free price and
the limit and all this, which is really good.
I guess we could add those.
If I click on edit, it opens up this uh
window, and I could actually change its
name if I want to, and then slug as well,
and then price is uh you know I can
change the price here and uh apply limit,
which is five, and then the description,
and then the features uh one per line.
I guess these features that you put here
are gonna show up on the pricing page.
So that's great.
Let's uh let's go to Pro Plan and change its
price to okay, it's in cents per month,
so we are gonna change it to 1495.
We're gonna save it, and then it shows up here
that it's now 1495 per month.
I'm gonna reload the page.
It is still working, so it means
that it has actually saved it.
Actually, I should log log out and
uh and then log back in to actually do
it, but I'm assuming that it's saved it.
I could delete it, which I am not gonna do
that, and I could create a new plan as well.
So let's try a new enterprise plan,
which says uh name is enterprise,
and then enterprise, then it's gonna be
you know say ninety-nine
dollars per month, apply limit is
gonna be of course minus one.
Okay, so this is not good because it's not able
to take minus one for unlimited.
So that's not good.
So we are gonna apply change it to We can get it
fixed by letting the letting Claude know
that this is not accepting the minus one.
So it's just a check that they have in that has
placed here to the check says
that it can only take uh numbers.
Uh it forgot to uh allow minus
one in there, so that's not good.
I wouldn't expect uh high end model to
have something like this, but then again,
we have set it to low, so I'm gonna let it go.
Description.
We are gonna this is for enterprise
and feature everything from unlimited
and then one on one customer support.
And we are gonna put this in there.
We have uh enterprise in here as well.
So it would be interesting
to see if um the pricing page
shows uh enterprise here, which is bad.
Uh that's not good because this is I wanna want
it to show here. And also it would be nice,
it would have been nice if I could basically
move the order, which uh it doesn't
provide, but that's that's fine.
That could be uh added something that I like.
So let's go to users uh and we
can see that there are two user.
One is the admin, that's us, and then there
is another user which is uh demo user.
And I should be able to edit and I'm it doesn't
have the edit feature here. So I should be able
to add it here, but it's not giving me
the added feature, which is not good.
However, it's actually giving me uh uh make
admin, you know, if I click on it,
this guy is also gonna become admin.
And if I click on it, it's this is
gonna become uh a regular user.
And if I do that, I won't be able to log in as
admin with any user, and that's gonna be bad.
So I'm not gonna do that, but I'm assuming good
software engineer actually going to check
if this user is the
only admin, then it would never allow them
to demote So fact that it's actually letting
me demote at least the button is there.
I don't know if it is
uh going to actually check at the time when
I'm gonna click that demo demo button.
Uh maybe it will and it won't let me do that,
but I'm not gonna take the risk right now.
So moving on,
then there are setting which actually says
that new signups are enabled or disabled.
So I could basically shut down the website
by saying that you know new signups are
disabled or you know enabled.
So that's a good feature, I guess.
Okay, so there is a button here that I could
click and it will go and retrieve the latest
and greatest uh jobs uh uh for the users.
So I could as an admin do that.
Uh more appropriate way to of doing
this when it goes to production is to
have a cron job or something, an automated job
that runs in the background, and it actually
goes and retrieves the jobs every hour or so
and updates the database so that the users
are notified as soon as any job actually
shows up that relates to their interests.
So okay, so this is what
admin looks like, I guess.
Okay, so there are jobs that we
could see, and then there is uh uh
admin panel here that we already saw.
So in the jobs, I think this jobs
tab is should be visible to the users as well.
So it is fill up filled up with the
dummy jobs, of course, for now.
Once I add the API key for app if I
it's gonna basically retrieve
the real jobs from here. But every time when
it's gonna run, it's gonna cost some money.
So we have to be careful how it wants.
So I guess probably because of
that it has it hasn't created any
cron job or automated job. It's basically
created at this button here,
which I could manually press.
But of course, we cannot go in in
production with something like
this. We will have to have some kind
of cron job that does it automatically in the
background. So yeah, that's what the admin
panel looks like. So I'm gonna log out from
here, and then we are gonna try to log in as
the user.
And let's see, the user is actually a demo
at a job glass.
I'm gonna say user one, and I'm gonna log in.
Okay, so we logged in.
So the user is in the unlimited uh uh plan.
We should have seen in the admin panel to see
if I could actually change the plan for the
user from the admin panel. Because if they
actually stop paying or something, it should
be automated when once they stop
paying, they should be or cancel job.
We'll we're gonna cancel the
subscription here and see how
it drops down. We will take a look.
So new jobs, it's showing new
jobs this week is 30, and you can
browse jobs, which actually brings it here,
which is all the same jobs that we saw before.
And then there is this uh applications
remaining, how many applications are
remaining? This user is on unlimited
plan, it's showing infinite here.
Uh jobs apply to is uh five. All time. So it's
pretending that you have already applied
for five jobs, and here are the jobs which
you have applied to. The only thing is that it
doesn't have any way to click on it. I'm not
able to click on these any of these links.
So I should be able to click on these links and
look at job listing details to see what those
jobs are about. So that's also
something that we need to work on.
Here's uh where it's a change plan.
So we are gonna see if we can
switch over to something
else. Let's see if we can switch over to choose
pro. Okay, so it actually switched over
to pro, but obviously since we don't have any
stripe keys right now, it's not going through
the payment processing and stuff like
that. It just switched over. If you go back to
the dashboard, it now says that I'm in pro
and I have 50 applications remaining.
Zero out of 50.
Even though it previously it was saying
that I had five already applied to, or here,
five are already applied to.
So it shouldn't be possibly saying 50
here. This is a problem, but it
could be because of the mock data.
Um sometimes
uh mock data handling is not very well,
but the actual data might work just fine.
So we'll have to be tested with the
real data and then you know ask uh Fable
to actually fix the issues.
and here you can see it still showing all
these jobs uh where a user could apply.
Of course, I'm right now it's um mock uh uh
listings, shows uh all
the job title address where it is located in
the salary range and the brief description.
It also has the link to the job listing.
If you click on it right now, obviously it's
just mock job, so it's not showing anything,
but it's supposed to take you to that listing
here, and then it has this apply button to each
and every job if you
want to apply. If you like that job, you can
just press apply and it will be applied.
Right now, of course,
again, it's uh just mock.
Uh, but it should be able to apply.
So yeah, so this is how what
the jobs uh page look like.
Now one more thing, if you
have to make it uh real app,
you will have to actually go into.env.
It has created this.env.example file.
You have to make a copy of it
or rename this file as.env.
And you will have to provide all this
information here that it that it's needed.
These are the API keys that you will need from
uh Stripe, as well as uh you need the API key
from Apify in order to basically get
the real data to make it a real um.
App.
Right now it's just basically
working with the mock data.
Once you do that, at this point it will
basically go and grab real job listing and uh
as well as actually make real payments for
the users who want that service from you.
So there is some work still
needs to be done here.
Uh overall, this looks uh a pretty good uh app.
Uh how does it compare to the
models that we had before?
If you ask me, I don't think there is anything
in here that I wouldn't be able to do with Opus
as well as with GPT 5.5.
If I had to build the same app with the
with these uh with this model, it would have
actually given me very much similar app.
Now the only difference is that I
started with just a small prompt and
uh you know let it uh uh build this.
Usually basically, as I said, I
went I go through create a PRD and
then I use that PRD to actually build the app.
But I think it's still it would
have come very close to I'm the
thing that really disappointed me
is that minus one thingy that we saw in
the that uh uh number of applications per
month uh field, that shouldn't be there.
I mean for a model which is so smart, it
shouldn't basically overlook such
a small thing that you know it
wouldn't allow minus one there,
even though minus one is a valid value, just
saying it there that minus one could be for
unlimited applications per month.
So that was a little bit uh of a bummer here,
but uh overall it did it performed very well.
To be fair to Fabble, I
mean we have kept it at low.
I think uh if I would have used Opus or GPT
five point five in low mode, which I never
do actually, it would probably not be
able to generate this kind of uh uh app.
I guess I would have to set it to medium or high.
So I guess I'm gonna use the Fabble
until June twenty second, for which it's
uh available to all the paid subscribers.
I don't think I'll be spending fifty dollars
per million token on this uh model uh you
know when it's not available freely
on the subscribe subscription
plan. Uh I don't think I'm gonna be basically
spending that kind of money to to build up.
Now if I'm making a very complex
app and I'm pay pa paid well for that,
then maybe I I might be able to justify using uh
Febleble uh you know based on the
API cost. This is my first experiment
with Fable model. I hope you liked it.
Uh let me know in the comments what do
you think about this model and uh
what else do you want me to build?
Uh if you want me to work with you on any of
your AI automation uh tasks. If you have a
business where you want to automate any of
its aspect if you're if something is costing
you too much money or if it is uh very slow and
uh very repetitive.
Then you could basically
always automate it with AI.
And it may cost you less and it can t definitely
save you a lot of time and money and uh free up
your staff to do something better.
Um so contact me and uh don't
forget to like and subscribe.